sidearmstats.com 2013-07-22

# Privacy Policy | SIDEARM Sports – The #1 Provider of College Athletics Websites

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like SIDEARM Sports . We are based in United States . Our principal activities are:

  * Colleigate Athletic Websites & Services
  * Streaming Media

Our privacy policy covers SIDEARM Sports and information collected on our Web sites:

SIDEARM Sports  
335 Hinds Hall  
Syracuse, NY. 13244  
www.sidearmsports.com & all websites developed by SIDEARM Sports 

Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.

The services and links of our Web sites 

Our Web sites do not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.Our Web sites may include links to third parties, however, we do not disclose any personal information to 3rd parties..

Automatic Collection of Information 

We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes:

  * Technical administration of the Web site
  * Customer administration
  * Marketing

Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.  

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please  click here 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.

Children’s Privacy 

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by:

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection of the child’s personal data
  * giving parents the option to consent to the collection and use of the child’s personal data for our internal use

We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personnal data from children on our Web site.

Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the table mentioned above, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure:

Confidentiality / Security 

This Site has implemented security policies, rules, and tecnical measures to protect hte personal data that we have under our control.  All aresas of the Website that collect or transmit personal information use 128 Bit SSL certificates. No credit card information is stored on Internet Consulting Services servers. Only those employees who need access to your information to carry out business functions are allowed access. There may be areas of the Website that require the user of a username and  password. It is our recommendation that you choose a strong password and that you do not share your password. It is important to recognize that whatever you transmit or disclose online could be collected and used by others or even unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the internet can ever be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us.  We have taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of our website and to prevent unauthorized access to information maintained by us.  These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data and to block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information.   We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.     We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

Access to the personal data we may hold about you 

You can ask us, by:

  * sending an email (sidearm@sidearmsports.com )
  * sending postal mail to this address (335 Hinds Hall, Syracuse NY 13244 )
  * calling this telephone number (315-443-1872 )

whether we are keeping personal data about you. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

  * erased
  * rectified or amended
  * completed

We do not reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

Privacy Compliance 

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy instrument.

Privacy Support 

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:  
sidearm@sidearmsports.com  
SIDEARM Sports  
335 Hinds Hall, Syracuse NY 13244  
315-443-1872

TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used by SIDEARM Sports.

Please note, each individual school or conference may use information for their own purposes. You will need to consult with that particular school/conference to learn more.

x volunteered by each visitor  
\- collected from public records or bodies  
\- collected from private organizations 

Primary personal data | Technical administration of the Web site  | Customer Administration  | Marketing   
---|---|---|---  
Name | 

x 

| 

x 

| 

x   
  
Gender or other personal information | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Address  | 

x 

| 

\- 

| 

x   
  
E-mail address  | 

x 

| 

x 

| 

x   
  
Phone/Fax number  | 

x 

| 

x 

| 

x   
  
Identifiers

X volunteered by each visitor 

| Technical administration of the Web site | Customer Administration   
---|---|---  
On-line identifiers | 

x 

| 

x   
  
Financial identifiers | 

\- 

| 

x
